And that's pretty much all. We also have the orientation to it, right? So I see the landscape.
No, I see portrait. So it suits my very image. And at the end, this is my prompt.
I also copy to keep it. And as you see, I also can choose from my models, but I go ahead with
Gemini and I click Generate. It's a start using partner models. Okay. And I wait until the image
editing is done. Something went wrong. So let's retry. Okay, so there's a problem. Let me first
switch the model. And when we're using firefly, we cannot add any kind of references more than
one. So let me remove myself, right? So another image of me in a suit. I remove this one.
And yeah, so this is my prompt now, right? So I just want to remove this light or this lamp
over here, right? And I click on Generate. And I wait until the editing process is done. And it's over.
And it's finished.
What does it say? Artist name detected, including artist names in your prompt does not meet our user
guidelines, artist names. There's an image of walking in Paris with Eiffel Tower in the background.
Where's the artist name? Okay. So let me remove the Eiffel Tower and stuff.
There's an image of aliens walking in Paris.
Um, so again, I click on Generate.
So is Eiffel Tower the name to any kind of artist? I don't know. But we again wait.
And as you see, we eventually got the result. So